

Thiago Oliveira

With over 10 years of experience in the tech startup industry, I have successfully scaled various business models such as SaaS, marketplaces, logistics, fintech, and proptech, catering to both B2B and B2C clientele. Throughout my career, I have taken on diverse roles including sales, product management, and growth.

基 Skills

- EXPERTISE Growth Marketing Product Management Sales Management Team Management Startups and Scaleups pace and culture - GROWTH MARKETING Performance Marketing

Performance Marketing and paid media SEO, Content and Organic demand generation CRM Social Media creatives Sales Development

- PRODUCT MANAGEMENT

Product Strategy and business alignment Managing GPMs and PMs Complex backlogs manamente MarTech Product Marketing PLG and Product Growth

- SALES MANAGEMENT SME and Mid Market B2B Sales B2C Sales Enterprise Sales

Work Experience

06/2023

Head of Growth CAFU

₩ Work Experience

05/2021 GOIÂNIA, GOIÁS, BRAZIL

Advisor Nectar

Advisor for Product and Growth Strategies

05/2022 - 06/2023 DUBAI, EMIRADOS ÁRABES UNIDOS

Head of Growth Huspy

Accountable for demand generation strategy and execution for all BUs (Mortgage and Real Estate) in all countries, mainly through paid media campaigns, SEO strategy, CRM and top of the funnel optimisation.

06/2021 - 05/2022 SÃO PAULO, BRAZIL

Director of Product Management Loft

Helped create 2 growth tribes from zero to 9 squads. Responsible for the mobile app, MarTech strategy, SEO/organic initiatives and 123i portal M&A (among other minor projects).

03/2020 - 06/2021 SÃO PAULO, BRAZIL

Senior Manager - Growth SumUp

Managed a 120+ people team responsible for the sales consultants program, the largest acquisition channel for SumUp Brazil in 2021. This included acquisition, communication and marketing, customer success, operations, support and business intelligence. We tripled the channel's results from 2020 to 2021 with marginal headcount increase.

08/2019 - 01/2020 SÃO PAULO AREA, BRAZIL

Growth Marketing Manager Loggi

02/2018 - 08/2019 SÃO PAULO E REGIÃO, BRASIL

Staff Product Manager - Growth Loggi

Work Experience

08/2017 - 01/2018 SÃO PAULO, SÃO PAULO, BRAZIL

Product Manager CargoX

PM in charge of internal products acting as technical leader for Product Owners.

06/2016 - 06/2017 SÃO PAULO AREA, BRAZIL

Head of Sales and Customer Success Runrun.it

Responsible for bringing a data-driven and analytical mindset to our Inside Sales, Channel Sales and Customer Success departments, I have helped scaling from 6 reps to a 40+people department with 5 coordinators.

- I worked closely with C-levels setting our sales strategies, OKRs and compensation models.
- I helped the coordinators managing theirs teams with a KPI based mindset, ensuring we have a continuous feedback culture based on KPIs instead of subjective analysis.
- I helped coordinators and reps working on their pipelines to meet short and long term goals.
- Along with SalesOps, I needed to make sure we continuously found the bottlenecks and improved our sales process, providing analyses on individual, team and company levels.

12/2014 - 06/2016 SÃO PAULO AREA, BRAZIL

Product Manager Runrun.it

Organizing and prioritizing product backlog, writing user stories and planning product roadmap based on investors', c-level's and team's interests and expectations using OKRs.

Managing the development team's daily operations aiming for a healthy, fair and productive environment.

Acted as Growth Manager, using my analytical mindset and product knowledge to help the company improve customer acquisition and retention.

02/2012 - 11/2014 SÃO PAULO AREA, BRAZIL

Product Manager Grupo DMC

Management of multiple simultaneous projects/products with small agile teams. Activities included organising sprint and product backlogs, benchmarking, pricing, implementation planning, recruiting, commercial presentations to key potential clients, writing User Stories/specs,

₩ Work Experience

conducting training workshops for new features, planning long-term training programs for existing users, acting QA lead, building test cases and performing exploratory tests.

08/2011 - 01/2012 SÃO PAULO AREA, BRAZIL

Product Manager Intercâmbio Global

Responsible for developing a new product. This includes supplier selection, pricing, marketing strategy and team training. Coordinated the company's e-Marketing and Social Media Management during that period.

Education

09/2021 - 03/2023

Executive Education | Stanford LEAD Professional Certificate Stanford University Graduate School of Business

09/2021 - 11/2021

MarTech Strategy: Leveraging Data and Technology in Marketing | Certificate Northwestern University

01/2021 - 01/2021

Product Leadership | Program Reforge

01/2019 - 01/2019

Growth - Retention + Engagement Deep Dive | Program Reforge

01/2018 - 01/2018

Course, Digital MKT and Product Growth Tera

01/2018 - 01/2018

Artficial Intelligence for Marketing and Growth | Course
Growth Tribe

01/2017 - 01/2017

Product Management | Formação Gama Academy

01/2013 - 01/2013

Business Intelligence | PEC FGV - Fundação Getulio Vargas

Education

01/2010 - 01/2012

Business Management | MBA BSP - Business School São Paulo

01/2005 - 01/2008

Tourism | Bachelor's Degree Universidade Anhembi Morumbi

01/2005 - 01/2006

Business Management in Tourism | Associate's Degree Universidade Anhembi Morumbi

Languages

English Full
Portuguese Native
Spanish Limited

Volunteering

01/2019 - 01/2019

Featured Speaker Product School

Founded in 2014, Product School is the world's first technology business school. As a featured speaker, I help inspire the next generation of Product Managers to create innovative products and apply best practices in their work.

https://www.productschool.com/instructor/thiagooliveira/

01/2017

Instructor Gama Academy

The largest recruitment, training and connection program for the the digital startups market. Gama Experience works as a selective trainee process for startups and technology companies. We select 100 professionals who are going through a complete immersion in the digital market, and, at the end of the program, the best students participate in recruitment processes for companies that recruit with Gama Academy.

01/2017 - 01/2018

Mentor SP Stars - Programa de mentoria para startups

SP STARS - Mentoring program for São Paulo Startups - http://www.spstars.co/